tekkenzaibatsu.com 2002-12-09

# Tekken Zaibatsu - Privacy Policy

Tekken is a copyright and registered trademark of Namco. All Rights Reserved. Tekken Zaibatsu is an unofficial site and is not related to Namco in any way, shape or form. Tekken Zaibatsu is not endorsed, nor supported by Namco.

Tekken Zaibatsu only claims ownership and copyrights to design elements, content and custom graphics that don't violate or infringe upon copyrights and/or trademarks made and claimed by Namco. All remaining content, media and images are the property and copyright of Namco. 

| 

The following are terms of a legal agreement between you and Tekken Zaibatsu. By accessing, browsing and/or using anything on this site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the terms below and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations. If you do not agree with these terms, don't use this site.

This website is to be used for personal information reference only. Using the materials on this website for any other use whatsoever is strictly prohibited without the express written consent and permission from Tekken Zaibatsu. 

| 

  * You are not allowed to link directly to any file, movie or image stored on any of our servers.
  * You are not allowed to use any content, HTML or design graphics for the creation of another website or commercial publication. However, if you wish to write a free Tekken FAQ based on the information on this site, you are welcome to do so as long as you give Tekken Zaibatsu proper credit for content used.
  * You are allowed to download media, such as images and movies made available through the gallery and media pages, and use them on your site UNALTERED so long as they're hosted on YOUR server.

| 

This site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We prohibit registration (Forum or Membership) by and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under 13. No information should be submitted to or posted by guests under 13 years of age, this includes submissions of publically viewed content such as public forum posts or registration for A tekken Zaibatsu membership.  
Tekken Zaibatsu does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever from our guests under 13 years of age. No information collected from guests under 13 years of age is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever.

The only individually identifiable customer information we currently collects are your IP address, submitted content and email addresses, which are volunteered by visitors wishing to participate in public forums, submit site content or sign up for free email services.

Tekken Zaibatsu does not sell, trade, lease or distribute any personal information of its registered forum users. However, any users who wish to participate in the public forums are required to provide a valid email address as a condition of participation, which will be publicly viewable along with any and all of their postings. 

Tekken Zaibatsu does not consider your IP as private personal information and therefore does not warrant its protection in this regard. We only collect IP addresses to facilitate system administration, to report aggregate information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user’s session will be logged, but the user remains anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our forum rules or terms of use or to protect our services and site.

Tekken Zaibatsu is an IronSilk Network Partner. Please review their [Privacy Policy](http://www.ironsilk.com/partners/privacy.html) before signing up for a Tekken Zaibatsu Free Membership. 

Visitors should be aware that when you are on Tekken Zaibatsu, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or click a link that takes you off our site. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online, that information can be collected and used by people you don’t know. While Tekken Zaibatsu strives to protect its users’ personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk. 

Tekken Zaibatsu uses WebTrends Live to analyze traffic to this web site. WebTrends Live does not create individual profiles for visitors. Unlike some tracking services WebTrends Live does not have a database of individual profiles for each visitor. WebTrends Live only collects aggregate data. For more information you can view the complete [WebTrends Live privacy policy](http://www.webtrendslive.com/privacy_policy.htm).
